Hey, uh, Holander, he's just, he's a human.
He's just like the rest of us.
We all make mistakes, right?
But we all deserve second chances.
In that spirit, Holander has agreed to donate ten million dollars to the Starlight House,
which, I mean, come on.
No, no, no, no.
Starlight lied to you just now.
She did.
I don't make mistakes.
I'm not just like the rest of you.
I'm stronger.
I'm smarter.
I'm better.
I am better.
I'm not some weak-need fucking cry baby that goes around fucking apologizing all the time.
And why the fuck would you want me to be?
What fucking commercial, Roger?
Go to fucking commercial?
Don't you dare stop rolling, Roger.
All my life, people have tried to control me.
My whole life, rich people, powerful people, tried to muzzle me, cancel me, keep me impotent and obedient,
like I'm a fucking puppet.
You know what, it worked.
Because I allowed it to work.
And guess what?
If they can control me, then you can bet your ass they can control you.
They already do, you just don't realize it.
I'm done.
I am done apologizing.
I am done being persecuted for my strength.
You people should be thanking Christ that I am who and what I am because you need me.
You need me to save you.
You do.
I am the only one who possibly can.
You're not the real heroes.
I'm the real hero.